teachthemdiligently.net 2018-08-23

# Privacy Policy - Teach Them Diligently

Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to keep your personal information confidential and understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations.

 **Our privacy policy explains:**

  * What information we collect
  * How we use that information
  * How long we keep your information
  * What information we share
  * The choices we offer

 **A. Types of Information We Collect and How We Use It**

  * website traffic patterns
  * statistics on the pages visited
  * details on the routes that users take to access and leave the website
  * Visitor details and demographics: country of origin and location, language spoken, browsers and computer platforms used
  * Traffic sources: referring websites, search engines, social networks, marketing/advertising campaigns or direct channels
  * Website content: traffic levels and activity on each page of the website
  * Engagement and retention metrics, such as how long visitors spend on certain areas of the website and how many pages they have visited in current and previous browsing sessions
  * Any other information our Customers choose to provide to our data tracking endpoints
  * Identity information such as email address as provided to us by our Customers through our analytics service

We collect some data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website, or the websites and online services where we display our advertisements. This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We collect certain personal information about you – but only when that information is provided by you or is obtained by us with your authorization. We use that information to fulfill the service that you have purchased or asked for such as a registration, men’s breakfast program or product purchase fulfillment. We may also use the information you provide to us to display advertisements to you that are tailored to your personal characteristics, interests, and activities.

 **B. Technologies We Use**

We use technologies such as cookies and pixels to keep track of your activities on our website and to serve you more relevant information.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your device for record-keeping purposes. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your device for an extended period of time. We and our third party partners use session cookies and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate and enhance the experience of our site, and to monitor and evaluate our website’s operation and use.

You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your internet browser’s “help” file. You may also decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website.

We reserve the right to use technological equivalents of cookies, including social media pixels. These pixels allow social media sites to track visitors to outside websites so as to tailor advertising messages users see while visiting that social media website.We reserve the right to use these pixels in compliance with the policies of the various social media sites.​

 **C. Parties to Whom We Disclose Information**

As a general rule, we do not disclose personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone. Your personal information or any information provided regarding any children or other family members is not sold at any time.

We may share aggregated non-identifiable information with ad partners, such as the number of users who visit a website or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the advertisers that you visit to learn about their data collection practices. We do not provide information to our advertisers about your activities. However, when you view or interact with an ad, the advertiser may infer that you engaged in the activities on its site that qualified you to receive the ad. We may also share information with other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.

 **D. Confidentiality and Security of Nonpublic Personal Information**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic personal information and any other information, to ensure our families that their privacy is a major part of the convention’s commitment to provide the finest service possible.

 **E. Opt Out Provisions**

While our organization only uses data to communicate pertinent information regarding attending one of our events or in fulfilling orders, any contact or attendee has the option to opt out of this communication at any time. However, the attendee assumes all risk for missing pertinent info regarding their registration such as start times, schedules, and other information.

You may use the NAI opt out tool [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), which will allow you to opt out of seeing personalized ads from us and from other NAI approved member companies.

You may opt out of receiving personalized ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services, including some that we may work with as Advertising Partners via the DAA website [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

European Interactive Advertising Digital Alliance (EDAA) – you may opt out via their [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) website.

 **F. Other Sites Policies**

We have no control over, nor do we bear any of the responsibility for the privacy policies and/or content of any sites or advertisers linked to or on our website, or the cookies these sites might set in your browser.

If you are outside the European Union and opt to receive any free resources, register for a webinar, register for a live event, or purchase any products sold by us on this Website, we will automatically enroll ​you to receive our free email newsletter. If you do not wish to receive this newsletter, you can unsubscribe anytime. We include an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send. If you ever have trouble unsubscribing, you can send an email to dpo@nullteachthemdiligently.net requesting to unsubscribe from future emails.

If you are in the European Union and opt to receive any free resources, register for a webinar, register for a live event, or purchase any products sold by us on this Website, we will only enroll ​you to receive our free email newsletter if you affirmatively consent to it. If you do not wish to receive this newsletter, you can unsubscribe anytime. We include an “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send. If you ever have trouble unsubscribing, you can send an email to dpo@nullteachthemdiligently.net requesting to unsubscribe from future emails.

 **G. Embedded content from other websites**

This site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

 **H. How long we retain your data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile and/or event registration profile. All users can see, edit, or request deletion of their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information. If you need help or have questions, write to dpo@nullteachthemdiligently.net.

 **By using this website, you consent to the processing of the data captured relating to your use of the website by us (and by those acting on our behalf such as Google Analytics, GoSquared and others) in the manner and for the purposes described above.**
